{
    "subject": "resource/Botch_(band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Botch (band) is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9823645353317261,
            "question": "Is Botch (band) a band from outside the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9784987568855286,
            "question": "Is Botch (band) an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8268749713897705,
            "question": "Where is Botch (band) from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8218203783035278,
            "question": "Botch (band)'s origin is in which nation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7133796811103821,
            "question": "Botch (band)'s musical style might be influenced by American culture. True or False?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6389831900596619,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Botch (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6070446968078613,
            "question": "What country is Botch (band) associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5905947685241699,
            "question": "From which country does Botch (band) hail?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4709261655807495,
            "question": "In what part of the world is Botch (band) based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4053550958633423,
            "question": "Where are Botch (band)'s roots?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Botch (band) is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8987_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what part of the world is Botch (band) based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8987_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=From which country does Botch (band) hail?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8987_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Botch (band) associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8987_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8987_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nAll the documents mention that Botch is an American band formed in Tacoma, Washington. This information supports the triple \"Botch (band) is from United States\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently indicate that Botch is an American band formed in Tacoma, Washington. This supports the statement that Botch (band) is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}